Guide to the Carl E. Ladd papers,1932-1943
Ladd, Carl E. papers, 1932-1943
- Carl E. Ladd papers
  - Farm Credit Administration., 1936-37 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    Myers, William I.; Farm Credit Administration; Federal Land Bank of Springfield.
  - Resettlement Administration., 1936-37 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Office of Experiment Stations., 1936-37 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    Jardine, James T.; United States Dept. of Agriculture, Office of Experiment Stations; Agricultural research.
  - Agricultural Conservation Act., 1936-37 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - United States Dept. of Agriculture, Extension Service., 1936-37 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - National Youth Administration., 1936-37 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - President's Office., 1937-38 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    Day, Edmund Ezra.
  - University Attorney., 1937-38 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Buildings and Grounds., 1937-38 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Comptroller., 1937-38 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    Rogalsky, George F.
  - Cornell University Treasurer., 1937-38 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Assistant Treasurer., 1937-38 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Office of the Dean., 1937-38 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Requisitions., 1937-38 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Business Office., 1937-38 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Dept. of Public Information., 1937-38 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    Boochever, Louis C.
  - Architecture., 1937-38 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Graduate School., 1937-38 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - New York State College of Veterinary Medicine., 1937-38 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    Hagen, William A.
  - Summer Session., 1937-38 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Traveling Fellowships., 1937-38 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Classifications of Salaries and Positions, State Colleges., 1937-38 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Salary Payments on a Ten Month Basis., 1937-38 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - New Buildings., 1937-38 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    Weatherlow, Hugh E.; Guterman, Carl E.F.
  - Farm and Home Week, 1938., 1937-38 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Bailey Hall Reservations., 1937-38 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Budget Requests., 1937-38 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Resolutions and Recommendations for Special Appropriations., 1937-38 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence Regarding Applications for Admission., 1937-38 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Arboretum Development, Correspondence and Committee Reports., 1937-38 (Box 13, Folder 33)
    Smith, Ralph C.; Ithaca Chamber of Commerce; Civilian Conservation Corps.
  - Miscellaneous Committees., 1937-38 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Committee on Conservation and Wildlife Management., 1937-38 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Committee on the Use of Calcium Meta-phosphate., 1937-38 (Box 13, Folder 36)
    Tennessee Valley Authority.
  - Agricultural Economics and Farm Management., 1937-38 (Box 13, Folder 37)
    Warren, George F.; Williamson, Paul.
  - James E. Boyle Article in Saturday Evening Post., 1937-38 (Box 13, Folder 38)
    Boyle, James E.; New York State Grange.
  - Agricultural Engineering., 1937-38 (Box 13, Folder 39)
    Riley, Howard W.; Robb, Byron B.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Agricultural Engineering.
  - Agronomy., 1937-38 (Box 13, Folder 40)
    Lyon, Thomas; Bradfield, Richard; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Agronomy.
  - Animal Husbandry., 1937-38 (Box 13, Folder 41)
    Morrison, Fred B.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Animal Husbandry.
  - Bailey Hortorium., 1937-38 (Box 13, Folder 42)
    Bailey, Liberty Hyde; Wiegand, Karl M.
  - Botany., 1937-38 (Box 13, Folder 43)
    Wiegand, Karl M.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Botany.
  - Appointment Books., 1937-38 (Box 13, Folder 44-49)
  - Dairy Industry., 1937-38 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    Stark, C.N.
  - Entomology., 1937-38 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    Readio, Philip A.; Matheson, Robert; Leiby, R.W.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Entomology.
  - Ornithology., 1937-38 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    Sutton, George M.
  - Agricultural Experiment Stations., 1937-38 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Director of Extension., 1937-38 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - New York State Agricultural Experiment Station., 1937-38 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    Guterman, Carl E.F.; Hedrick, Ulysses P.; Nebel, Bernard R.; Tressler, Donald K.
  - Farm Bureau, State Leaders., 1937-38 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    Flansburgh, Earl A.
  - Home Bureau, State Leaders., 1937-38 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    Powell, Grace A.
  - Junior Extension, State Leaders., 1937-38 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Lincoln D. Kelsey., 1937-38 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Montgomery Robinson., 1937-38 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    Robinson, Montgomery E.
  - Charles Taylor, Elmer Phillips., 1937-38 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    Taylor, Charles A.; Phillips, Elmer S.; Cornell School for Missionaries.
  - Publications Office., 1937-38 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    Adams, Bristow.
  - Forestry., 1937-38 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    Hosmer, Ralph S.
  - Floriculture and Ornamental Horticulture., 1937-38 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Plant Breeding., 1937-38 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    Emerson, E.R.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Plant Breeding.
  - Plant Pathology., 1937-38 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Pomology., 1937-38 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Pomology.
  - Poultry Husbandry., 1937-38 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    Hutt, Frederick B.; Mumford, Herbert W.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Poultry Husbandry.
  - Resident Instruction., 1937-38 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Rural Education., 1937-38 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    Butterworth, Julian E.
  - Rural Social Organization., 1937-38 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    Sanderson, Dwight; Cottrell, Leonard S.
  - Vegetable Crops., 1937-38 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    Thompson, Homer C.
  - New York State College of Home Economics., 1937-38 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    Rose, Flora; Henry, Mary F.
  - Hotel., 1937-38 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - A Miscellaneous., 1937-38 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - New York State Agricultural Society., 1937-38 (Box 14, Folder 27)
    Eastman, Perley M.; Van Wagenen, Jared Jr.; Whetzel, Amy; David, Millard; New York State College of Agriculture.
  - American Agriculturist., 1937-38 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    Eastman, Edward R.; Babcock, Howard E.; New York State, Dept. of Conservation; New York State Grange; Publicity; Milk prices.
  - Agricultural Missions Foundations., 1937-38 (Box 14, Folder 29)
    Reisner, John H.; Irvine, F.R.
  - American Express Company., 1937-38 (Box 14, Folder 30)
    Morsbach, A.A.
  - American Rose Society, Test Gardens., 1937-38 (Box 14, Folder 31)
    Hatton, R. Marion.
  - B Miscellaneous., 1937-38 (Box 14, Folder 32)
    Brockway, George A.; Sadd, C.E.; American Forestry Association; Willowbrook Ayrshire Farm.
  - H.E. Babcock., 1937-38 (Box 14, Folder 33)
    Babcock, Howard E.; Roosevelt, Franklin D.; Hiscock, Frank H.; Lehman, Herbert H.; Day, Edmund Ezra; Grange League Federation; New York State Grange; Norris-Doxey Act.
  - C Miscellaneous., 1937-38 (Box 14, Folder 34)
    New York State Dairy Goat Association.
  - New York State Conference Board of Farm Associations., 1937-38 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - D Miscellaneous., 1937-38 (Box 14, Folder 36)
    Donlon, Mary H.; Dreyfus, Victoria; American Agriculturist.
  - Dartington Hall., 1937-38 (Box 14, Folder 37)
    Elmhirst, Leonard K.; Dartington Hall; Devon Cattle.
  - Dairymen's League Cooperative Association, Inc., 1937-38 (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Democrat and Chronicle., 1937-38 (Box 14, Folder 39)
    Skeffington, Leo B.
  - H.S. Duncan Memorial Fund., 1937-38 (Box 14, Folder 40)
    Porter, Roy A.
  - E Miscellaneous., 1937-38 (Box 14, Folder 41)
    Elmhirst, Richard.
  - Empire State Gas and Electric Association., 1937-38 (Box 14, Folder 42)
    Nixon, Maurice W.; Smith, George H.; Rural electrification; Farm electrification.
  - Empire State Potato Club., 1937-38 (Box 14, Folder 43)
  - Epsilon Sigma Phi., 1937-38 (Box 14, Folder 44)
    Hart, Van B.
  - F Miscellaneous., 1937-38 (Box 14, Folder 45)
  - American Farm Bureau Federation., 1937-38 (Box 14, Folder 46)
  - New York State Farm Bureau Federation., 1937-38 (Box 14, Folder 47)
    Foster, Edward S.; Black, Albert G.
  - Farm Credit Administration of Springfield., 1937-38 (Box 14, Folder 48)
    Munger, H. Bruce; Lamb, George W.; New England Dairies.
  - G Miscellaneous., 1937-38 (Box 14, Folder 49)
  - Grange League Federation., 1937-38 (Box 14, Folder 50)
    Milliman, Thomas E.; McConnell, James A.
  - New York State Grange., 1937-38 (Box 14, Folder 51)
    Miller, Stella F.
  - National Grange., 1937-38 (Box 14, Folder 52)
    Taber, Louis J.
  - H Miscellaneous., 1937-38 (Box 14, Folder 53)
    Hiscock, Frank H.; Ithaca Production Credit Association; Norris-Doxey Act.
  - F.C. Huyck and Sons, Experimental Sheep Farm., 1937-38 (Box 14, Folder 54)
    Morrison, Frank B.; Rumpf, E.F.; Ashby, H.M.; Kenwood Experimental Sheep Farm.
  - New York State Home Bureau Federation., 1937-38 (Box 14, Folder 55)
    Putnam, Anna G.
  - I Miscellaneous., 1937-38 (Box 14, Folder 56)
  - J Miscellaneous., 1937-38 (Box 14, Folder 57)
  - K Miscellaneous., 1937-38 (Box 14, Folder 58)
  - L Miscellaneous., 1937-38 (Box 14, Folder 59)
  - Association of Land Grant Colleges and Universities., 1937-38 (Box 14, Folder 60)
  - Association of Land Grant Colleges and Universities., 1937-38 (Box 14, Folder 61)
    Creel, Cecil W.; Warburton, Clark; Guterman, Carl E.F.; Walton, T.O.; Bankhead-Jones Act.
  - Association of Land Grant Colleges and Universities., 1937-38 (Box 14, Folder 62)
    Warburton, Clark; Creel, Cecil W.; Wallace, Henry A.; Hills, J.L.; Bankhead-Jones Act; Hatch Act.
  - Committee on Relations, Confidential Correspondence with Reuben Brigham and Others., 1937-38 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    Brigham, Reuben; Creel, Cecil W.; Warburton, Clark; Eisenhower, Milton S.; Ickes, Harold L.; Agricultural Adjustment Administration.
  - Association of Land Grant Colleges and Universities., 1937-38 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    Creel, Cecil W.; Ramsower, H.C.; Mann, Albert R.; Wallace, Henry A.; Walton, T.O.; Agricultural Adjustment Administration; Association of Land Grant Colleges and Universities.
  - Association of Land Grant Colleges and Universities, Special Committee on Federal-State Relations in Agricultural Activities., 1937-38 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    Walton, T.O.; Jardine, James T.; Creel, Cecil W.; Warburton, Clark; United States Dept. of Agriculture; Norris-Doxey Act.
  - Association of Land Grant Colleges and Universities, Special Committee on Federal-State Relations in Agricultural Activities., 1937-38 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    Creel, Cecil W.; Hutchison, C.B.; Brigham, Reuben; Eisenhower, Milton S.; Blaisdell, Donald C.; United States Dept. of Agriculture.
  - M Miscellaneous., 1937-38 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - A.R. Mann., 1937-38 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    Mann, Albert R.; General Education Board; Farm and Home Week.
  - Milk Situation, 1937., 1937-38 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    Taylor, Charles A.; Metropolitan Cooperative Milk Producers Bargaining Agency; Dairy Farmers Union; Milk prices.
  - N Miscellaneous., 1937-38 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    Neurath, Hans.
  - National Association of Manufacturers., 1937-38 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Near East Foundation., 1937-38 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - New York State Horticultural Society., 1937-38 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    McPherson, Roy P.
  - New York State Holstein-Friesian Association., 1937-38 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    Burke, James D.
  - Norris-Doxey Bill., 1937-38 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    Norris-Doxey Act.
  - Northeastern Poultry Producers Council., 1937-38 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    Mapes, William S.; Rice, James E.
  - Northeastern States Experiment Stations., 1937-38 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - O Miscellaneous., 1937-38 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - P Miscellaneous., 1937-38 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    Poletti, Charles.
  - Post Standard., 1937-38 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - R Miscellaneous., 1937-38 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Regional Laboratory for Pasture Development, Northeastern States., 1937-38 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    Hills, J.L.; Cardon, P.V.
  - Regional Poultry Laboratory, Northeastern States., 1937-38 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    Guterman, Carl E.F.; Mohler, J.R.; Bankhead-Jones Act.
  - S Miscellaneous., 1937-38 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - State Schools., 1937-38 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - T Miscellaneous., 1937-38 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    Treman, Robert E.
  - Tompkins County Development Association., 1937-38 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    Williams, Fred A.; Williams, Hugh J.
  - Town Highway Superintendents' School., 1938 (Box 15, Folder 26)
    Hurd, Thomas N.
  - U Miscellaneous., 1937-38 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - V Miscellaneous., 1936-38 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - W Miscellaneous., 1937-38 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - XYZ Miscellaneous., 1937-38 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Governor of the State of New York., 1937-38 (Box 15, Folder 31)
    Lehman, Herbert H.; Babcock, Howard E.; Milk industry.
  - Board of Regents Inquiry., 1936-38 (Box 15, Folder 32)
    Gulick, Luther; Hill, David S.; Betten, Cornelius; New York State Agricultural Experiment Station; Cornell University Agricultural Experiment Station.
  - New York State Dept. of Agriculture and Markets., 1937-38 (Box 15, Folder 33)
    Noyes, Holton V.
  - New York State Dept. of Education., 1937-38 (Box 15, Folder 34)
    Getman, Arthur K.; Horner, Harlan H.; Wilson, Lewis A.; New York State Agricultural Experiment Station.
  - New York State Dept. of Education., 1937-38 (Box 15, Folder 35)
    Wilson, Lewis A.; George-Deen funds.
  - Budget Director., 1937-38 (Box 15, Folder 36)
    Weber, Lewis S.
  - Dept. of Conservation., 1937-38 (Box 15, Folder 37)
    Osborne, Lithgow; Gabrielson, Ira N.; New York State Dept. of Conservation.
  - New York State Dept. of Health., 1937-38 (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - New York State Public Service Commission., 1937-38 (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - New York State Dept. of Public Works., 1937-38 (Box 15, Folder 40)
    Brandt, Arthur W.
  - Agricultural Conservation Committee, New York State., 1937-38 (Box 15, Folder 41)
    Flansburgh, Earl A.; Agricultural Adjustment Administration; Resettlement loans.
  - United States Dept. of Agriculture., 1937-38 (Box 15, Folder 42)
    Auchter, E.C.; Reed, O.E.; Wallace, Henry A.; Wilson, M.L.; Flansburgh, Earl A.; United States Dept. of Agriculture, Soil Conservation Service; United States Dept. of Agriculture, Office of Experiment Stations; Clark-McNary Law; Devon Cattle.
  - Office of Experiment Stations., 1937-38 (Box 15, Folder 43)
    Jardine, James T.; United States Dept. of Agriculture, Office of Experiment Stations; Bankhead-Jones Act.
  - Extension Service., 1937-38 (Box 15, Folder 44)
    Brigham, Reuben; United States Dept. of Agriculture, Extension Service.
  - Farm Credit Administration., 1937-38 (Box 15, Folder 45)
  - Soil Conservation Service., 1937-38 (Box 15, Folder 46)
    Jones, John P.; United States Dept. of Agriculture, Soil Conservation Service.
  - Resettlement Administration, Farm Security Administration., 1937-38 (Box 15, Folder 47)
    Chapin, Oscar H.; New York State Farm Security Advisory Committee; Rehabilitation loans.
  - Secretary of the Treasury., 1937-38 (Box 15, Folder 48)
    Morgenthau, Henry Jr.
  - Office of the Dean., 1938-39 (Box 15, Folder 49)
    Catherwood, Martin P.; Parker, George W.
  - Requisitions., 1938-39 (Box 15, Folder 50)
  - President's Office., 1938-39 (Box 15, Folder 51)
    Day, Edmund Ezra; Ickes, Harold L.
  - Cornell University Attorney., 1938-39 (Box 15, Folder 52)
  - Buildings and Grounds., 1938-39 (Box 15, Folder 53)
  - Cornell University Comptroller., 1938-39 (Box 15, Folder 54)
  - Bailey Hortorium., 1938-39 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Botany., 1938-39 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    Randolph, Lowell F.; Wiegand, Karl M.
  - Dairy Industry., 1938-39 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Entomology., 1938-39 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    Palm, Charles E.; Alien, Arthur A.; Roses Incorporated; Robertson-Pittman Bill.
  - Cornell University Agricultural Experiment Station., 1938-39 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    Guterman, Carl E.F.; Bankhead-Jones Act.
  - New York State Agricultural Experiment Station., 1938-39 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    Parrott, Percival J.; Carpenter, D.C.; Nebel, Bernard R.; Tressler, Donald K.; Hershey, Ora E.; Dahlberg, Arthur C.; Breed, Robert S.; Experiment Station Day.
  - New York State Cooperative Extension Service., 1938-39 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Farm Bureau, State Leaders., 1938-39 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    Fricke, Richard F.; Flansburgh, Earl A.; New York State Farm Bureau Federation.
  - Junior Extension, State Leaders., 1938-39 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Home Bureau, State Leaders., 1938-39 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Publications Office., 1938-39 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - E.A. Bates., 1938-39 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    Bates, E.A.; Indian reservations.
  - Kelsey, Lincoln D., 1938-39 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Robinson, Montgomery E., 1938-39 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Taylor, Charles A., 1938-39 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Farm Practice., 1938-39 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Floriculture and Ornamental Horticulture., 1938-39 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    White, Edward A.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Floriculture and Ornamental Horticulture.
  - Forestry., 1938-39 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    National Farm School.
  - Library., 1938-39 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Plant Breeding., 1938-39 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    Rollins, Emerson A.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Plant Breeding.
  - Plant Pathology., 1938-39 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    Massey, Louis M.; Warren, George F.
  - Pomology., 1938-39 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    Heinicke, Arthur J.
  - Poultry Husbandry., 1938-39 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    Tisdel, Alton P.; Hutt, Frederick B.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Poultry Husbandry.
  - Resident Instruction., 1938-39 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Rural Education., 1938-39 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    Butterworth, Julian E.; National Youth Administration.
  - Rural Social Organization., 1938-39 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    Anderson, Walter A.; Sanderson, Dwight; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Rural Social Organization.
  - Vegetable Crops., 1938-39 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Home Economics., 1938-39 (Box 16, Folder 28)
    Rose, Flora; Schumaker, Doris; New York State College of Home Economics; American Home Economics Association.
  - Home Economics, Appointments and Resignations., 1938-39 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence Regarding Applicants for Admission, Agriculture and Home Economics., 1938-39 (Box 16, Folder 30)
    Rasp, Ruth M.; Lehman, Herbert H.
  - Hotel., 1938-39 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - New York State College of Veterinary Medicine., 1938-39 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Miscellaneous Committees., 1938-39 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Arboretum Committee., 1938-39 (Box 16, Folder 34)
    Weatherlow, Hugh E.
  - Committee on Reorganization of Work in Biological Sciences., 1938-39 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - College Land Use, Committee to Study Needs., 1938-39 (Box 16, Folder 36)
    A.I. Reed Farm.
  - Faculty., 1938-39 (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - Alumni Association., 1938-39 (Box 16, Folder 38)
    Cornell University, Alumni Association; Cornell Day.
  - Athletic Council., 1938-39 (Box 16, Folder 39)
    Babcock, Howard E.; Lynah, James.
  - Budget, 1939-40., 1938-39 (Box 16, Folder 40)
    Wiegand, Karl M.
  - Bailey Hall Reservations., 1938-39 (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - Farm and Home Week, 1939., 1938-39 (Box 16, Folder 42)
    Graves, Frank Pierrepont; Lehman, Herbert H.; Roosevelt, Eleanor; Farm and Home Week.
  - Traveling Fellowships., 1938-39 (Box 16, Folder 43)
    Staker, E.V.; Boynton, Damon.
  - Requests for Special Research., 1938-39 (Box 16, Folder 44)
    McNeal, Edward K.
  - A Miscellaneous., 1938-39 (Box 16, Folder 45)
  - New York State Agricultural Society., 1938-39 (Box 16, Folder 46)
    Eastman, Perley M.
  - Applications for Positions from Foreign Countries., 1938-39 (Box 16, Folder 47)
    Emergency Committee in Aid of Displaced Foreign Scholars.
  - American Agriculturist., 1938-39 (Box 16, Folder 48)
  - B Miscellaneous., 1938-39 (Box 16, Folder 49)
  - Babcock, Howard E., 1938-39 (Box 16, Folder 50)
    Munn, M.T.; Grange League Federation.
  - C Miscellaneous., 1938-39 (Box 16, Folder 51)
    Christensen, Chris L.; Cornell Club of New York.
  - New York State Conference Board of Farm Organizations., 1938-39 (Box 16, Folder 52)
  - Constitutional Convention., 1938-39 (Box 16, Folder 53)
  - Crop Protection Institute., 1938-39 (Box 16, Folder 54)
  - D Miscellaneous., 1938-39 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    Donlon, Mary H.
  - Dartington Hall Elmhirst, Leonard K.; Warren, George F.; Devon Cattle., 1938-39 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Democrat and Chronicle., 1938-39 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    Skeffington, Leo B.; Duncan Memorial Fund.
  - Dairymen's League Cooperative Association, Inc., 1938-39 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    Sexauer, Fred H.; Dairymen League News.
  - Henry Strong Denison Fellowship., 1937-38 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    Jameson, Elsa Denison.
  - E Miscellaneous., 1938-39 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Empire State Potato Club., 1938-39 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    Porter, Roy A.; Lehman, Herbert H.; Potato industry.
  - Empire State Gas and Electric Association., 1938-39 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    Farm electrification.
  - Epsilon Sigma Phi., 1938-39 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - F Miscellaneous., 1938-39 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - American Farm Bureau Federation., 1938-39 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    Agricultural legislation.
  - New York State Farm Bureau Federation., 1938-39 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Farm Economic Association., 1938-39 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    American Farm Economic Association.
  - Fruit Grower's Conference, 18 Aug 1938., 1938 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Farm Credit Administration of Springfield., 1938-39 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    Thomson, Edward H.; Disaster Loan Corporation.
  - G Miscellaneous., 1938-39 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Grange League Federation., 1938-39 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    Milliman, Thomas E.
  - General Motors - Cornell World Price Index., 1937-38 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - H Miscellaneous., 1938-39 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - I Miscellaneous., 1938-39 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Institute of Rural Affairs, Board of Advisers., 1938-39 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Ithaca Savings Bank., 1938-39 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    Cook, G. Louis.
  - International Conference of Agricultural Economists., 1938-39 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    Elmhirst, Leonard K.; Ladd, Lucy F.
  - J Miscellaneous., 1938-39 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - K Miscellaneous., 1938-39 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - L Miscellaneous., 1938-39 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Association of Land Grant Colleges and Universities., 1938-39 (Box 17, Folder 27)
    Brigham, Reuben; Creel, Cecil W.; Warburton, Clark; Eisenhower, Milton S.; Hills, J.L.; New York State Soil Conservation Committee; Extension work; Bankhead-Jones Act.
  - Association of Land Grant Colleges and Universities., 1938-39 (Box 17, Folder 28)
    Creel, Cecil W.; Walton, T.O.; Bankhead-Jones Act.
  - M Miscellaneous., 1938-39 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Milk Situation 1938., 1938 (Box 17, Folder 30)
    Metropolitan Cooperative Milk Producers Bargaining Agency; Agricultural Adjustment Administration.
  - N Miscellaneous., 1938-39 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - New York Breeders Association., 1938-39 (Box 17, Folder 32)
    Duck, R.W.
  - National Association of Manufacturers., 1938-39 (Box 17, Folder 33)
    Wright, J. Handley.
  - New York Farmers, Inc., 1938-39 (Box 17, Folder 34)
    Appleton, Francis R.; Day in the Country; Pasture research.
  - New York State Horticultural Society., 1938-39 (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - New York State Jersey Cattle Club., 1938-39 (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - New York State Seed Improvement Association., 1938-39 (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - New York State Holstein-Friesian Association., 1938-39 (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - New York State Vegetable Growers' Association., 1938-39 (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - New York State Fair., 1938-39 (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - P Miscellaneous., 1938-39 (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - R Miscellaneous., 1938-39 (Box 17, Folder 42)
    World's Poultry Congress.